polestar.com 2014-05-03

# Privacy policy

|  |   
---  
  
## 

General  
  
Polestar respects the privacy of individuals and does not collect or manage any personal data unless it has been provided to us voluntarily by the individual concerned.  If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use this website.  
  
## 

Personal data  
  
Polestar will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you, e.g. your name, address, telephone number or email address, through this website unless you have provided it to us voluntarily. In order to respond to your questions or fulfil your requests, it may be necessary to ask for personal information such as your name, address, e-mail address and telephone number. Polestar may use this information to respond to your requests, or to contact you via mail, e-mail or phone to fulfil your request. Polestar does not now or in the future intend to sell, rent or market personal data about you to third parties.  
  
## 

Information collected automatically  
  
Polestar may collect information about you, which is generic in nature and is not personally identifiable, during normal website usage. Such data is not telling us who you are or revealing any other information of a personal nature. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet Browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and your IP address.  
  
## 

"Cookies"  
  
When you view this website, or any other website linked from this website, we may store some information on your computer in the form of a “cookie”. This information allows us to measure website activity to tailor information to suit your individual preferences. Cookies may tell us the time and length of your visit, the pages you look at on our websites, and the website that referred you to our website. The goal is to save you time and provide you with a more meaningful visit.

A cookie is a small text file which the website you are visiting saves on your computer. Cookies are used by many websites to give visitors access to various functions. The information contained in the cookie can be used to monitor a user’s surfing behaviour. There are two types of cookies. One kind of cookie saves a file for an extended period on your computer and is used, for example, with functions which describe what information is new since you last visited the particular site. The second kind of cookie, also called “session cookie” is stored temporarily in your computer’s memory during the time you visit a website. The session cookie is for example used to keep track of which language you have chosen on the website. Session cookies are not stored for a long time and disappear when you close your browser. Polestar uses cookies e.g. to record visitor statistics.  

You can set your computer to block cookies. However, this means that Polestar cannot guarantee that all areas of our web site will function as intended. The procedure for blocking cookies will depend on what browser you are using. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.  
  
| | |
